

# **Muhammad Achyadi Rahmat**

# PHP / Laravel Developer

Github : github.com/RahmadahyaWeb Mobile: +6281247189174

Email : <a href="mailto:thelastpc24@gmail.com">thelastpc24@gmail.com</a>
Portofolio : <a href="mailto:rahmadahyaweb.github.io">rahmadahyaweb.github.io</a>

#### **SUMMARY**

I am an active student from Politeknik Negeri Banjarmasin, majoring in Electrical Engineering with a focus on the Diploma 3 program in Informatics Engineering. With approximately one year of experience, I possess skills in developing websites using the PHP programming language, specifically Laravel framework. I am known for my ability to quickly learn and adapt to new situations, making me a valuable asset to any team.

#### **EDUCATION**

- Politeknik Negeri Banjarmasin Department of Electrical Engineering, Diploma Program in Informatics Engineering (2021 Present).
- SMK Telkom Banjarbaru Computer and Network Engineering (2018 2021).

#### **EXPERIENCES**

#### PT PLN PERSERO WILAYAH KALIMANTAN SELATAN DAN KALIMANTAN TENGAH

(January 2020 - March 2020)

 As an <u>intern</u> in the commercial division, I am responsible for managing customer data using VBA Excel.

#### **CODE CLIMBERS**

(October 2022 - Present)

 As the <u>team leader</u> of the CODE CLIMBERS Community. I am responsible for instructing and guiding my team in the creation of both <u>static and dynamic</u> websites.

#### POLITEKNIK NEGERI BANJARMASIN

(May 2023 - Present)

 As the <u>team leader</u> of the Project Based Learning (PBL) Program. I am responsible for mentoring and teaching my team in the development of an <u>alumni information</u> system website.

#### **CERTIFICATION**

• Competent in the area of Programming and Software Development with competency as a: Junior Web Developer, on behalf of the Indonesian Professional Certification Authority, Professional Certification Institution of BPPTIK (2022).

#### **SKILLS**

# **Programming Language:**

MySQL

- PHP
- Javascript

### **Version Control:**

**Database Management System:** 

• GIT

# Web Development:

- HTML
- CSS
- Vanilla Javascript
- Frontend framework (Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS)
- Backend framework (Laravel)

#### **COURSE & TRAINING**

- Fullstack Web Developer CODEPOLITAN & KELASFULLSTACK.ID
- Blog Like a Pro KARTEIL BY PARSINTA
- Laravel: Panduan Belajar Framework Laravel 10 **DUNIAILKOM BY ANDRE PRATAMA**
- PHP & Laravel Sampai Mahir PROGRAMMER ZAMAN NOW

#### **PROJECTS**

- Alumni Information System (SISAMI)
- Employee Information System
- Simple Blog Implementation
- Todolist (Taskerisk)
- Personal Portofolio